this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them now this is exciting i can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next
with a charted course awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cut a path across the grand line
to the new world separated from the rest of his crew luffy has finally arrived at marine ford to
rescue his brother ace thanks to a final charge from whitebeard's associates success seemed to be
within luffy's grasp but then the unthinkable happened and admiral akainu landed a fatal blow
against luffy's brother the man that gold d roger was waiting for it's not you teach not a damn chance
forgive me my sons i raised a fool and i couldn't take responsibility
but you boys gave me everything i could have ever wanted out of life
i am deeply grateful
goodbye my sons
the show begins blackbeard's blood is revealed
you guys in the head office watching this this marine ford business is gonna change the world
so it's true after all not only ace but whitebeard too
unreal they killed him a news spread like wildfire falling on ears that could scarcely believe the
words ace son of the great gold roger fell in battle alongside whitebeard who was powerless
to save him extra get ready to issue an extra we just received some breaking news
whitebeard was killed shortly after fire fist ace and the marines have claimed victory
he's really dead
yeah
this crew is done for
there's peace again
if the navy can take care of whitebeard
then the rest of the pirates will follow
while many celebrated those who saw these events unfold with their own eyes
stand transfixed their mouths agape words frozen on their lips
bon voyage whitebeard
his name was edward newgate in his prime he stood against even the king of the pirates
his crew was his family and he fought beside them into the ripe old age of 72 the world knew him as whitebeard
he had stepped boldly into marine ford and brought the walls of the navy headquarters down around him and yet despite his superhuman efforts
the navy forces aided by the seven warlords proved too strong
ah what a day it's the birth of a new world or the death of an old one and look i think today's party may have some
life in life in life in life in life yet
we've certainly got some villainous figures here to keep things interesting i'm sure
you wouldn't guess by looking at him
but that blackbeard is quite a thinker
i don't like this why do i get the feeling things just a concern for the worst
also
what whitebeard said before he died troubles me
the one piece the one piece is real
now it's only a matter of time before word spreads to the rest of the world
he's riling up all the pirates just like roger did
speaking of pirates how do you think blackbeard fits into this whole equation
surely he didn't show up just to kill his old captain right
that bastard marco for what it's worth we all share your sentiment but it's not the time for revenge
yeah i get it let's go save your tears and hurry up you fools you haven't forgotten your
captain's final orders have you no distractions we'll be setting sail as quickly as we can understood
forgive me old man forgive me ace despite my efforts i was powerless to save either of you
at the very least i vow that no more harm will come to luffy
don't let a single pirate get away fire the cannons and wipe them out
uh
oh
Hey! Hey, where are you going? Captain!
Where do you think, stupid? Someplace far away from here!
My plan to kill Whitebeard is shot, obviously!
So we're running away?
I was so close!
Enjoy this black hole!
Now's your chance! Go! Take Whitebeard out!
Come on, the guy's half dead already.
Just fly over that pit and stab him in the back while he's busy.
Hey, stop telling me what to do!
Dealing with Whitebeard is a delicate matter!
You've got to wait for the right time!
Also, I'm not half as strong as you think!
No more airfield, White's not against me!
I see! You were just waiting for him to lose his power before you jumped in.
Hey, let us toss you over there!
Okay, Captain. Now it's time to fly. Ready?
Not yet!
My arm!
Since when are dying old men so damn strong?
No, of course he's strong.
That's what makes this guy a legend.
That's what makes this so scary.
Yeah, I'm scared! I admit it!
I'd rather dig a hole, crawl in, and live the rest of my measurable life in there than face this guy!
I don't care if you think I'm pathetic, damn it!
I don't need you losers around anyway!
Captain Buggy!
He's crying! Is it our fault?
Aha! He's teaching us a lesson about sympathy!
Seeing Whitebeard suffering filled him with pity, and humanity triumphed over savagery. Beautiful!
His message is engraved upon my soul!
But he left, fearing we wouldn't understand!
Son of a gun!
Our inner spirits have been corrupted, longing for violence when we should have been thinking of mercy!
He had a shot at fame and fortune, but he understood that the cost of his personal integrity was a price too high to pay!
Because material gains are ultimately meaningless, and public acclaim is fleeting in these trying times!
I've seen the light, Captain! It's as if I've been reborn!
Share more of your wisdom with us!
The life turns are going!
Come back!
That old codger was tough as nails! I thought he'd never die!
A minor delay, yes, but scarcely unexpected. Now for the fun part!
Yeah, let's give them a magic show they'll never forget!
Be careful! Who knows what they're planning!
You monster! Haven't you done enough to Pops?
Watch carefully, it's a good trick!
So good, in fact, it's gonna shake the whole world down to its core!
Whatever this is, it's not good!
Is he doing something to Whitebeard's corpse in there?
Now, now. I know you're curious, but please don't interrupt.
Don't get too cocky, pirates!
He joined the Seven Warlords just so he could betray us!
Whatever he's up to, you can bet it won't be good!
I can't wait!
So what happens if this plan doesn't work?
We disband?
Ha!
Keep moving!
We're almost there!
Luffy!
I know it hurts right now, but you must carry on, for in a world without Ace, your courage will be needed.
Tomorrow, and every day after.
Fire!
It's a heavy weight, but one I'm confident you can bear.
Jinbei, I know I might not make it out of this alive.
I'm sorry, but if I die, would you look after my brother for me?
I fear you misjudge my character, Ace.
I mean no disrespect, but I may not be as charitable as you think.
I'm certain you care for your brother, but we live in a world of pirates.
I offer my aid to those I hold in high regard, but only to them.
Although your death was a tragedy, it did not sway my feelings.
And yet, it would appear I found the answer to your request all the same.
Rest easy.
Your brother is worthy of whatever favor my humble strength can grant.
I wish I could heal Luffy myself, but I will have to entrust him to you.
Pacifistas! Aim for Straw Hats!
Jinbei betrayed us! He's just like any other pirate now!
So kill him if need be!
Curfume Femur!
That's enough, Hancock!
One more of those and we open fire on you too!
The execution was a success, and Whitebeard is dead too.
I consider pushy men to be an extreme turn-off.
I've done all that I can, Jinbei.
Take good care of my darling.
We've got room on this ship over here!
Coming!
What the?
Dammit! And we were so close too!
You mean we're stuck?
Well, we've got to do something!
Aokiji's coming!
Somebody stop him!
We have to run!
Go!
Did you really think you could get away from me?
Why don't you save yourself some trouble and let me kill you?
Hand over dragons, son, and I may decide to spare you.
Aka'inu? I thought Pops killed him!
But how did he survive the fall?
Did he come out of the ground?
Those lava powers freak me out!
Jinbei! A generous offer, but I must refuse!
You aren't the only tenacious one here! I've decided to protect this boy no matter the cost!
Have it your way, then. I won't ask twice!
Oh jeez! Admiral Aka'inu won't be able to save you!
I may decide to spare you!
Aka'inu? I thought Pops killed him!
But how did he survive the fall?
Did he come out of the ground?
Those lava powers freak me out!
Jinbei! A generous offer, but I must refuse!
You aren't the only tenacious one here! I've decided to protect this boy no matter the cost!
Have it your way, then. I won't ask twice!
Oh jeez! Admiral Aka'inu won't be satisfied till Straw Hat's six feet under!
And you know him! Once he's got his eyes set on someone, there's no escape!
Come on, Luffy!
You're not gonna lay a finger on Straw Hat!
Pops wanted us to protect him!
That's right! And if he's Ace's brother, then he's our family, too!
This family crap again? Listen to yourselves!
You act brave now!
But if I recall, you were happy to leave your beloved brother and father to their fates and run away to save yourselves!
What?!
Go to hell!
Huh? Do we have a plan B?
Useless cowards, out of my way!
Make room!
Coming through! Emporio face-proof synthesis!
If I may, I believe I can be of assistance here.
Great scissors!
Keep those magma-covered paws of yours off of Straw Boy!
This kid is history and his father will be next!
Tell...
Wing-ga!
He's been pushing himself since Impel Down.
He's passed his limit physically and emotionally.
It's a wonder he's still alive.
One more hiccup and we could lose him!
If something were to happen on my watch, I could never show my giant face to his father again.
As Dragon's comrade, it's my duty to protect his family.
I feel the same.
I have a job to do here so I'd appreciate it if you would step aside!
Unless you're looking to die too!
My goodness, you're sassy!
You think you're hot stuff? You ain't seen nothing yet, Magma Boy!
Because this queen is on fire!
I do believe it's the moment we've all been waiting for.
Come on, Captain! Hurry up and show us already!
Ladies and gentlemen, mostly gentlemen, we are grateful for your patience.
Captain Teach and his merry men present to you a stunning spectacle.
The likes of which you've never seen.
One, two, ta-da!
What did he do?
He was doing something in there, but what?
The Whitebeard's body looks the same.
Blackbeard's too, I think.
It's been fun!
Huh?
The Warlord thing, I mean.
You played your part well.
But as you'll see, I don't need you anymore.
See?
Black Hole!
What's happening?
This one here you all know.
It's my dark dark fruit power.
But this...
Just watch!
No, it can't be!
Yah!
I, ha-hah-hah-hah-hah-hah!
Ha-hah-hah-hah.
Yah!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
An earthquake, that's the power of the tremor tremor fruit!
I thought if you had two telephone powers you would die!
And how do you take them for Whitebeard in the first place?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
I can't believe you pulled it off!
Seems I chose the right side after all.
Though seeing as I was getting tortured every day,
I didn't have anywhere to go but up.
Moroon!
He stole that power from Pops!
I know, but how?
That isn't normal, is it?
A hand of darkness to call forth the void.
A hand of light to shake the heavens and rend the earth.
Both are mine, and the world will tremble with my every step.
Only a fool would dare defy me!
I don't know how he did it, but he did it!
You can't fake having a power like that!
But does he know that we don't?
Sam!
We beat Whitebeard, but so what?
It's even worse than before!
But hold on.
I thought if you tried to get a second devil fruit power,
then your body would, like, blow up.
Yeah, for normal people, that's how it works.
But you know as well as I do
that teaches anything but normal.
And with that body of his,
he can pull a trick we couldn't even dream of.
He's probably been planning this thing for ages now.
Got your attention now, Z-
Ha ha ha ha ha!
This is a wake-up call to all the boring peace lovers,
the half-assed pirates,
the fat-headed fools in world government,
the ignorant masses!
This is a nightmare.
It just has to be.
We all must answer to the hand of fate.
Z-
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
And fate has chosen me to conquer this world!
This isn't fair.
The Navy won.
Roger's son is dead and so is Whitebeard.
We're all doomed.
Even the Admirals can't fight someone like that.
He's a monster!
A demon!
Damn it!
I thought this war was over already.
How many people have to die
before we can stop these pirates for good?
I told myself this execution was a necessary evil,
but after all this,
we're even worse off than when we started.
Z-
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Yeah!
Having stolen Whitebeard's devil-proof power,
Blackbeard rampages to his heart's content.
Meanwhile, Aka-Inu and the Navy
massacre the pirates in the name of justice.
As the battlefield becomes a living nightmare,
Kobe stares on in horror,
voices echoing in his head.
On the next One Piece,
the insatiable Aka-Inu,
Lava Fist Pummel Luffy,
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!